megathe.me 2019-06-28

# 

## PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: 05/24/2018

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to [www.mediatemple.net](http://www.mediatemple.net/) (the “Site” or “Media Temple”) owned and operated by Go Daddy Operating Company LLC. It describes how Media Temple collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

###  **EU-U.S. & Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield**

Our parent company, Go Daddy Operating Company, LLC (and our related entities, including GoDaddy.com, LLC, Wild West Domains, LLC, Blue Razor Domains, LLC, Starfield Technologies, LLC, Domains by Proxy, LLC, Outright, Inc., Locu, Inc., GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. and Mad Mimi, Inc.) participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Privacy Shield Framework. We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on each Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and to view our certifications, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield List](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Media Temple is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Media Temple complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Media Temple is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Media Temple may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

###  **A. Personally-Identifiable Information:**

Media Temple typically receives specific data about its website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, open a customer support inquiry ticket, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a credit card to pay for services, submit your resume, or request certain types of information. When you provide personally-identifiable information to Media Temple through one of our websites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. In most cases, you will be given the opportunity to select whether you do, or do not, want Media Temple to use this information for additional purposes.

Media Temple will not, however, sell or trade your personally-identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to the visitor or others.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

#### These services may include:

  * Fulfilling orders
  * Payment processing
  * Providing customer service
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Fulfilling subscription services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Providing cloud computing infrastructure

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at privacy@mediatemple.net.

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. On those Media Temple sites where you may provide Media Temple with credit card or other sensitive information via the web, Media Temple protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET).

####  **Targeted Advertisements**

Absent any instructions from you, Media Temple may use information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by the Media Temple family of companies, Media Temple venture companies, Media Temple authorized agents, and other goods and services providers with whom Media Temple has relationships and whose offerings might be of interest to you. Media Temple and our third party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)]. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

####  **Supplementation of Information**

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personally identifiable information you submit to us with information from third party sources (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

####  **Communicating with you**

We may contact you directly or through a third party service provider regarding products or services you have signed up or purchased from us, such as necessary to deliver transactional or service related communications. We may also contact you with offers for additional services we think you’ll find valuable if you give us consent, or where allowed based upon legitimate interests. You don’t need to provide consent as a condition to purchase our goods or services. These contacts may include:

  * Email
  * Text (SMS) messages
  * Telephone calls
  * Automated phone calls or text messages

You may update your contact preferences with respect to receiving communications from us by signing into your Account Center and visiting "Contacts" page.

###  **B. Website Analytics:**

We use multiple web analytics tools provided by service partners such as Google Analytics to collect information about how you interact with our website or mobile applications, including what pages you visit, what site you visited prior to visiting our website, how much time you spend on each page, what operating system and web browser you use and network and IP information. We use the information provided by these tools to improve our Services. These tools place persistent cookies in your browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone other than the service provider (ex: Google for Google Analytics). The information collected from the cookie may be transmitted to and stored by these service partners on servers in a country other than the country in which you reside. Though information collected does not include personal data such as name, address, billing information, etc., the information collected is used and shared by these service providers in accordance with their individual privacy policies. You can control the technologies we use by utilizing settings in your browser or third-party tools, such as [Disconnect](https://disconnect.me/disconnect "Disconnect"), [Ghostery](https://www.ghostery.com/ "Ghostery") and others.

 **Cookies and similar technologies** on our websites and our mobile applications allow us to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Services. This allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings, a better experience on our sites and mobile applications, and to collect, analyze and improve the performance of our Services. We may also collect your location (IP address) so that we can personalize our Services.

You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our site.

Internet browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings are usually found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your internet browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful. Otherwise you should use the 'Help' option in your internet browser for more details.

If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, you will need to delete your cookies using your internet browser settings.

####  **More information about cookies**

  * Useful information about cookies, including information about deleting or blocking cookies, can be found at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "All About Cookies")
  * A guide to behavioral advertising and online privacy has been produced by the internet advertising industry which can be found at: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ "Your Online Choices")
  * Information on the ICC (UK) UK cookie guide can be found on the ICC website section: <http://www.international-chamber.co.uk/our-expertise/digitaleconomy>

#### **Do Not Track notifications**

Some browsers allow you to automatically notify websites you visit not to track you using a “Do Not Track” signal. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.

###  **C. Your (mt) Media Temple hosted website, server, bulletin boards, forum, Third-Party Sites:**

Information that you disclose in a public space, including on any blog, bulletin board, chat room, or website Media Temple may host for you as part of your Media Temple services, is available to anyone else who visits that space. Media Temple cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations. Additionally, Media Temple websites contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to Media Temple. Media Temple cannot protect any information you may disclose in these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

On those sites where you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like, Media Temple will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and nonproprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this Policy, Media Temple assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, contact us at privacy@mediatemple.net. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.  

###  **D. Exceptions and Limitations:**

Notwithstanding the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, Media Temple (i) cooperates fully with state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to Media Temple) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Service, and (ii) takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws, Media Temple may be required to disclose personally identifiable information. In addition, Media Temple may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate Media Temple; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Media Temple or others. In connection with the potential sale or transfer of any of its interest in mediatemple.net, and ac.mediatemple.net and other sites owned by the company, Media Temple reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including, but not limited to name, address information, and other information you provided to Media Temple) to a third party that (i) concentrates its business in communication products or services; (ii) agrees to be Media Temple's successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by Media Temple; and (iii) agrees to the obligations of this Policy.

###  **E. Transfer of Data Abroad:**

If you are visiting this site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers.

###  **F. Access, Update or Delete Data:**

To easily access, view, update, or close your account, or to update your contact preferences, please sign into your Account Center and visit Contacts and Billing.

To request a copy of your account data (EU customers only) or delete your account, please contact us at privacy@mediatemple.net. If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.

If you are unable for any reason to access your Account Center, you may also contact us by one of the methods described in the “Contact Us” section below.

We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.

###  **G. Data Protection Authority:**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) and believe we maintain your personal data subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority, the UK's Information Commissioner’s Office, as noted below:

Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF

Phone: 0303 123 1113

###  **H. Updates:**

We may update this Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

####  **Contacting Us**

 **GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc.**  
14455 North Hayden Road Suite 100  
Scottsdale, AZ 85260  
P: 877.578.4000
